Hello, welcome to Market Sons
Tamil. I am your Rahul.  Today in this
video, we will talk about Elevate from ICIC number,
Riya 3.0 from Ival, and
Active 1 Max from IEB.  Detailed comparisons of these three products
, their
positives and negatives, which one is the
best in terms of parameters?  Who
has a hot tub?  We
are going to discuss in detail what kind of premiums are available.  You may
also find this video useful when making a buying decision
.  So, do
n't skip and watch the whole thing.  If this is
your first time visiting my channel
, please subscribe to the channel and
click the bell icon.  So,
you'll get a notification when I upload a video
.  Anyone can
purchase life health insurance
.  Please feel free to contact us and ask
where we can get service.
I have a wonderful team
.  We will provide 100% after-purchase service
assistants on our side
.
You already know better than to purchase from us.  And if you found
this video useful, please like it
.  Tell us your thoughts in the
comments.  Share.
Don't forget to say hi.  Let's go into the video
.  Before we look at product features,
let's look at how the company is performing.
In terms of claim settlement ratio, they are also
ahead of Burla Cleara.
Network hospitals are again ready to do business with Barla
.  Complaint volumes
ICICI Lombard is
registering complaints.  The second Aditya
Barla Munavata Niwaba is coming.  Inker
Claim Ratio Again ICICI Bank is
scoring a good score.  The second is Aditya
Barla Munavata Niwapa.  Overall,
Adi Birla gives a good
performance.
You have a second chance, ICICI Bank, or a third
chance.  So, those who need it, please
pass the details and watch.
For futures,
they start from the coverage limit, which comes first.  Coverage limit for ICICI Lambard
Derivatives is up to 5 lakh 3 crores
maximum.  This ratio is 3.0.
They give 5 lux, they give 10 lux,
and then they give unlimited cover,
then they give a minimum of 5 lux and a maximum of 2
lux. Regarding the minimum and
maximum entry age, there are only
three products. If you want to come and become an adult, you must
be 18 years old.
You can enter Elevate for a maximum of 125 years
.
You can enter up to a maximum of 99 years at a ratio of 3.0.   There is
no such limit.   Even if
you want to enter these three policies as a child, you
must have completed 91 days.  After that,
after you enter, you can come here and continue until you reach the age of 30 and remove the child yourself
.
As for the unique selling point, ICICI
Lampard Elevate offers
an optional cover called Infinite Care
.  So, if a large bill comes up during the life of the policy, for
example, a single bill of 50 lakhs or 1 crore, then
this
insurance company will come and settle it for you
.  You can only use one bottle in your lifetime
.  This is an optional cover that can be
purchased by those who need it.
For Ratio 3.0, you have an
extraordinary features policy.
One of the features that you have is
Lock the Clock. This comes in and
when you enter at a certain age, they
set a premium
. For example, if you enter at the age of 25, you will have a premium.  And normal general comes to
the policy and adds an age bracket, which is a
premium change.  There will
be a premium for 25 to 30, 30 -
35 will be a premium.  That kind of
change will happen to you.  But, under this
policy, you will continue to pay whatever premium you entered at until you make a claim,
until the first claim is made
.  If
you entered at the age of 25, and
you come and
take your first class at the age of 50, you will
pay the same premium until then.  However,
adjusted for inflation, premiums
may increase slightly at times.
Rendavata, Booster Plus.  This booster
plus, this rider comes to
you, maximum, up to 10 times
, you can come and carry forward your annuity, with some
issue, and
take it away.  For
example, if you have taken a cover of 10 lakhs and
spent 2 lakhs in the
first year, then in the
second year, you carry forward the remaining 8
lakhs and take it.
Similarly, the
maximum is up to 10 lakhs. So, if this comes,
you will take a cover of 5 lakhs and
take a cover of 10 lakhs. This
is the booster plus use.  If
you use ReShor 3.0 for unlimited coverage, you
won't need a booster.  Because the base policy
gives you unlimited power.
And again, when
you come to Reshore Browser,
you can see the Restore or Rebuild option and how it works when you look at the features.  So, in the same way,
there are two unique selling points called super reload and super credit.  We can see this too when we
look at our Deidilda features
.  For road ambulances, all
three policies
cover you up to some extent.  The air
ambulance will come and give you 3.0 lakhs to 5 lakhs for hospitalization
.  ICC Lampard is
coming to Elevate and giving riders.  You can come and
get those who need it.
You don't have air ambulance cover.
This is a negative thing.
As for the room rent limit, both the Niwaba
Ratio 3.0 Active Max and Up
Some Inns will cover you
.  But there is an issue with the IC number elevation
.  They
only give you a single private AC in the base policy
.  But to overcome that,
you can use a room modifier like a rider.  So if you
choose the room option, you
can choose any room you want.  So if
you're ever going to go over the limit with Ice,
definitely come to the room and
make sure there's no limit.  Definitely
make this rider sauce.  All three policies provide you with coverage for IC Domiciliary
Day Care Treatment, Modern
Treatments, and Robotic Surgery
.  They provide 2 plus hours of hospitalization in BS4 3.0
.  You will only be covered if
you are hospitalized for more than 30 minutes
.  But at least a disease should be
diagnosed and treated for it
.  They wo
n't just give you a diagnosis.
Pay attention to that.
You already have some kind of disease.
For that, you
will be admitted and have those two words of treatment,
for example dialysis, and all that
will be covered under this.  Pro Claim
Bonus comes to you, and if
you don't claim every year, they
come to you and give you a 20%
bonus.  The maximum will
go up to 100%.  And Riot 3 0
Booster Plus, I already
told you that you can come and carry forward the insurance that you haven't used, and
take it up to a maximum of 10 minutes.  I already
told you, didn't I? The unique
selling point is that you have
super credit on the Ultiper Active One Max
.  This will come and give you a 100% bonus
.  Whether you claim it or not,
you can carry forward the maximum of 500%
.  ICICI Bank's Lambard No
Claim Bonus benefit is
very popular this time of year, so it's
clear that it's a great deal.  As far as the refill and recharge
options are concerned, you
get all three policies and they
give you unlimited times.  No matter how much you
drink, your base phone will be restored to use when you are admitted and discharged
.  For example,
you have 10 lakhs.  You spent ₹3 lakh
.  No, you just spent a total of 10
lakhs, and they will
give you that 10 lakh rupees back as soon as you recharge.  No, they will
give you the balance of ₹3 lakh.  It will be replayed.  So, when this
comes, you can use that base sum in the same year for the same
disease or a different
disease
.  So this has arrived in all three
cities.  There
is no flaw in any of the three policies.
As for the ride, ICIC will
come to the Lambard Elevate and give you a rider
.  Those who need it
can take it.  There is no cover at all in Ratio 3.0
.  And it's in Active One Match
.  Those who need a rider
can also take it.
As far as dental is concerned, all three policies
only cover you for injuries and accidents
.  We don't cover all of that by doing window treatments, cleaning our
roots, and getting color treatments
.  For free
and paid hospitalization,
you have a ratio of 3.0 for 60
and 180 days and with Active Max,
you have 90 and 180 days of coverage
.  As a consumer,
you will need to purchase an extra rider for both policies, including Claim Protect, which comes with a built-in policy
.
Those who need it can take it.
My advice is to definitely take it.
As for the materiality cover,
you have a material cover in ICICI Lambard Elevate
.  So they'll give you 10% off some items
.
As for the maximum cap, the
waiting period for 1 lakh is 2
years.  So if you need a material cover,
you can order this rider.  Both
the 3.0 and Opti Pack
come with
no material cover.  For annual culture,
you can also opt for an optional cover rider in the ic televangelist
.  Both policies
come with built-in coverage.  All three
come with limits for you.  Plus
you can go cashless.
As for the wellness coverage, they
give you both IC number deliver and Riot 3.0.
They give you specific activities like
how many gallery visits you make in a day,
how many steps you walk in a day, and so on. If
you have achieved that, then you have a chance to get a discount of up
to 30% during the maximum renewal time
.
As far as riders are concerned, you definitely need to upgrade your IC number, and
you should be able to use that room modifier
.  So, it arrived and I
gave it to you.
As for the maternity waiting period,
I said two years, right? So there is a
rider to reduce that by one year.
And also, if you already
have an existing disease, for example, hypertension
, diabetes,
hyperlipidemia, obesity, coronary artery
disease, then at that time,
you can mention that disease and get
covered for 31 days
.  So,
those who need a rider jamsta for that can take it.
And with Ratio 3.0, if
you have a pre-existing disease, they will
load it to cover it from day one
.  This is an
extraordinary feature, and if they
pay extra loading for any disease and underwrite it,
you will get cover from day one
.  And for specific
diseases, they generally put a two-year waiting
period on all companies and
all products, so you can come back and make a two-
year waiting period a one-year deal
.  And if you already have
an existing disease, the
waiting period is generally three years
.  That waiting period can be
shortened to one year or two years
.  There's a rider for that here too.
And for the Alpha Active One Max,
you will have a pre-
existing disease exemption
.  So, you
can come and make a profit in one or two years.  And there will
be a two-year waiting period for specific illnesses.  That
can be done in a year.  And if
you have any hypertension, diabetes,
hyperlipidemia, COPD, obesity,
corona disease, and asthma, you can
take out a rider to cover it from day one.
As for the premiums, I
came and took two examples for 10 lakh sum insured and 10 lakh
cover
.  In the first example, the husband is
33 years old, the wife is 29 years old, the head is
3 years old, and in the second example, the husband is
63 years old, the
wife is 58 years old.  Now
I
have given you three examples.  Those
who need it on the screen, please pass and watch.
We looked at the comparison with the product futures.  Now let's
come to the verdict.
As for performance metrics, the principal comes and creates a
comprehensive performance metric
register.  The
clear winner in terms of product features is Nibarisho 3.0
.  Lock the Clock Booster Plus
has a Rio Parvar external feature.
So, if you're an individual who wants a product with a good feature
set and a somewhat average
experience,
then you should
definitely go for the Rear 3.0
.  The second time, the president came and said, "Active
One Max" and you
don't have any medical coverage.  But overall,
this product has a whole bunch of features
.  Everything you need is there.
And if you understand that your climbing experience is
decent,
you can come and
play an active one match with Artibarla.
As for the iclapat elevator, the
draw back is a bonus.  They give you a bonus of
just 20% on that policy and claim-
free years.  Maximum
100% is also a negative thing.
Understanding that, those of us at our age can
definitely come and
try to write down your ICI number for a long-term plan for every period of time you need maternity leave.  I hope
you will really enjoy this video
.  If you are Yusufullah, please like
the video
.  Tell us your thoughts in the comments
.  If any of your friends and
family are researching to purchase health insurance,
share this video with them.  So that
they have the opportunity to be useful
.  Thank you, hello.